elements.org 2016-05-28

# FACTS

                                                                                                        Rev. 04/2016
                       WHAT DOES ELEMENTS FINANCIAL
FACTS                  DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                   Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal
                       law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law
                       also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal
                       information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?                  The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the
                       product or service you have with us. This information can include:
                      • Social Security Number and income
                      • account balances and payment history
                      • credit history and credit scores
                       When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share
                       your information as described in this notice.
How?                   All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run
                       their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial
                       companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons
                       Elements Financial chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                Reasons we can share                                                       Can you limit this
              your personal information                    Does Elements share?                sharing?
For our everyday business purposes —
such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                     Yes                          No
your account(s), respond to court orders and
legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes —
                                                                     Yes                          No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                   Yes                          No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes —
                                                                     Yes                          No
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes —
                                                                     No                      We don’t share
information about your creditworthiness
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                   No                      We don’t share
Questions?                 Call (800) 621-2105 or go to elements.org/privacypolicy

Who we are
Who is providing this notice?   Elements Financial
What we do
How does Elements Financial     To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and
protect my personal             use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These
information?                    measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Elements Financial     We collect your personal information for example, when you
collect my personal
                               • open an account or deposit money
information?
                               • pay your bills or apply for a loan
                               • use your credit or debit card
                                We also collect your personal information from others, such
                                as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?  Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                               • sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes —
                                  information about your creditworthiness
                               • affiliates from using your information to market to you
                               • sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                State laws and individual companies may give
                                you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                      Companies related by common ownership or control. They
                                can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                               • Our affiliates include credit union service organizations
                                  such as Elements Financial Services, LLC; Credit Union
                                  Student Choice, LLC; and CO-OP Financial Services.
Nonaffiliates                   Companies not related by common ownership or control.
                                They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                               • Elements Financial does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing                 A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies
                                that together market financial products or services to you.
                               • Our joint marketing partners include investment, insurance,
                                  and other financial services companies.
